[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the 16th president of the United States?", "correct_answer": "Abraham Lincoln", "incorrect_answers": ["Andrew Johnson", "James Polk", "Ulysses P. Grant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This sci-fi movie was directed by James Cameron and filmed at a decommissioned power plant in England.", "correct_answer": "Aliens", "incorrect_answers": ["Dawn of the Dead", "The Terminator", "The Witches of Eastwick"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Thomas Lennon appeared in the 2001 comedy Out Cold.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Transcription is the process of creating what from the DNA template?", "correct_answer": "RNA", "incorrect_answers": ["Fatty Acids", "Protein", "A Double Helix"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pablo Escobar was a very important cocaine dealer. The 2009 movie Killing Pablo tells a version of Escobars murder. It stars this Oscar Wining actor from  Europe.", "correct_answer": "Javier Bardem", "incorrect_answers": ["Daniel Day-Lewis", "Jean Reno", "John Malkovich"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mace is one of the spices, derived from the fruit of this evergreen tree, indigenous to tropical southeast Asia and Australasia.", "correct_answer": "Nutmeg", "incorrect_answers": ["Paprika", "Primrose", "Poppy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is contrology?", "correct_answer": "Pilates", "incorrect_answers": ["the study of freshwater life", "the study of social controls", "the study of dates"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color is Carters prom dress in the movie Princess Protection Program?", "correct_answer": "blue", "incorrect_answers": ["yellow", "pink", "green"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the literal translation of the word lanigera in the name of the chinchilla species Chinchilla lanigera?", "correct_answer": "Wearing a woolen coat", "incorrect_answers": ["Long-tailed", "Having long ears", "Sleeping in straw"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2006 movie set at the Alpha Kappa Gamma sorority house is a remake of the 1974 film of the same name.", "correct_answer": "Black Christmas", "incorrect_answers": ["When a Stranger Calls", "Halloween", "Funny Games"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is Phobos a satellite of Mars?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1997 movie American Werewolf in Paris was filmed entirely in France.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]